shift, but I imagine it's just market share dynamics in a country that we have, of course,
other competitors. Thank you. Thank you. So next question,
consultations.
Next question comes from the line of Seamus Fernandez from Guggenheim Securities. Please go
ahead. Thanks for the question. So, Faz, I guess the question on our side is, just given the
substantial valuation increases that we've seen across biotech in the last year,
how should we be thinking about the business development opportunities as you see going
forward? You know, you talked about the BD focus.
Really being no change, but certainly one change in that mix has been valuation. So just trying to
get a better sense of how you're thinking about that and the kind of risk that Novartis needs to
take going forward. And then just, you know, a quick question that I wanted to ask on the
Pella Carson side of things. You know, it's a composite endpoint. And, you know, my recollection
was we saw, you know, a muted benefit or maybe not muted, but a teens benefit. And I think that's a
benefit with SGLT2s, but an outsized benefit in the heart failure population on cardiovascular
death. How might that kind of an outcome play out? Or do you see that as a potential outcome
for Pella Carson, you know, as the data reads out in the second half of this year? Thanks.
Thanks, Seamus. So I think on valuation, I mean, look, when I reflect over nine years,
I would say that the
price of assets that don't have minimal clinical data has gone up quite dramatically. You see now
ourselves and our peers doing upfronts that are over a billion dollars for assets that have
limited or no clinical data, which is, I think, you know, if you took the long arc of the sector,
a significant shift, which I think just means you have to have higher levels of conviction in the
science and differentiated. Something that you believe is unique and differentiated,
in our case, the three deals we did this year, so, you know, with Pickivation, we believe that
there is an opportunity to address more of the mutant, a pan-mutant kind of approach in PI3
kinase-driven breast cancer with Accelergy to tackle with hopefully a much higher efficacy